emagine-entertainment.com 2019-12-16

# Privacy Policy - Emagine Entertainment

This Privacy Policy explains how your information is collected, used, and shared by Emagine Entertainment (“Emagine,” “we,” “our,” or “us”) when you access or use the website <http://www.emagine-entertainment.com/>, use our mobile apps that link to this Privacy Policy, or join an Emagine rewards or membership program (collectively, the “Services”).

By accessing or using the Services, you agree to this Privacy Policy.  IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SERVICES.

  1.  **The Information We Collect.**

How we collect and store information depends on how you use the Services.  Several categories of information are collected from you or the device that you use to access the Services, as described below.

 ** _Information You Provide_**

We may collect information you choose to provide to us when you use the Services.  This may include your name, email address, phone number, and zip code, as well as any other information that you choose to provide.  If you enroll in our rewards or membership programs, or purchase a ticket online, you may have to provide us with additional information including billing information and financial account information, and, to administer these programs, we may track your purchase and attendance information.  You also may have the opportunity to provide us with certain demographic information such as your birthday, the theaters you visit, and what movies you like.  The decision to provide us with information is optional; however, if you elect not to provide certain information, you may not be able to access certain content or features of the Services.  You may provide us with information about yourself when you engage in various activities on the Services, including when you:

  * Enroll in one of our membership or rewards programs;
  * Log-in to your account;
  * Create or edit your user information;
  * Complete an online form, such as a party booking request;
  * Request certain features (e.g., newsletters, updates, and other products);
  * Contact customer support; or
  * Enter contests or sweepstakes.

 ** _Automatically-Collected Information_**

We may automatically collect certain information about the computer or devices you use to access the Services, even if you are not logged in.

 **Device/usage information.** We may automatically collect certain information about: (a) the computer or devices (including mobile devices) you use to access the Services, such as:  IP addresses, unique device identifiers, browser types, browser language, operating system, Internet service provider; and (b) clickstream information related to the ways in which you interact with the Services, such as: referring and exit pages and URLs, platform type, language, the number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages and content viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time you used the Services, the frequency of your use of the Services, and error logs.  As described further below, we may use third-party analytics providers and technologies, including cookies and similar tools, to assist in collecting this information.

 **Location information.   **When you use our mobile apps we may collect different types of information about your location, including general information (e.g., IP address, zip code) and more specific information (e.g., GPS-based functionality on mobile devices used to access the Services), and may use that information to customize the Services with location-based information, advertising, and features. If you access the Services through a mobile device and you do not want your device to provide us with location-tracking information, you can disable the GPS or other location-tracking functions on your device, provided your device allows you to do this. See your device manufacturer’s instructions for further details.

 **Cookies and other electronic technologies.** When you use the Services or view our emails, we and our vendors use persistent and session cookies and other similar technologies (such as Web beacons, pixel tags, and clear GIFs) for various purposes including to: (a) analyze use of the Services; (b) customize the Services to your preferences; and (c) control the advertising displayed on the Services, as well as advertisements that may be displayed on other websites. Cookies are files that websites and email services may send to your computer or device to uniquely identify your browser or to store information or settings on your device.  As we adopt additional technologies, we may also gather information through other methods.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies by visiting the Help portion of your browser’s toolbar. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in, customize, or use some of the features of the Services. By using our Services with your browser set to accept cookies you are consenting to our use of cookies in the manner described above.

 ** _Information from Third Parties_**

We may obtain additional information about you from third parties such as marketers, partners, researchers, and others.

 ** _Anonymous or De-Identified Data_**

We may anonymize and/or de-identify information collected by the Services or via other means so that the information does not identify you.  Our use and disclosure of aggregated and/or de-identified information is not subject to any restrictions under this Privacy Policy, and we may disclose it to others without limitation for any purpose.

  2.  **How We Use the Information We Collect.**

We use the information that we collect in order to:

  * Provide you with the services and products you have requested and send you information about your relationship or transactions with us;
  * Customize the content and advertising that you see on the Services;
  * Notify you about new features of the Services, special events, special promotions (e.g., birthday gifts), and send you newsletters;
  * Generate and review reports and data about our user base and Services usage patterns;
  * Analyze the accuracy, effectiveness, usability, or popularity of the Services and perform research regarding our users and how they use the Services;
  * Improve the content and features of the Services and develop new services;
  * Provide you with e-mail or direct mail marketing communications about our products and third-party products and services that we believe may be of interest to you;
  * Help prevent fraud and enforce the legal terms that govern your use of the Services; and
  * Administer and troubleshoot the Services.

We may combine information that we collect from you with other information we obtain from third parties and any other product or service we provide to further improve the relevance and effectiveness of products, services, and advertisements offered on or through the Services.

  3.  **Information Sharing and Disclosure.**

We may share your information for the following purposes:

  *  **Service Providers.** We may share your information with service providers that help us deliver the services you request, such as credit card processors, advertisers, analytics providers, data management services, web hosting, and web development. We furnish service providers with the information needed for them to perform these services, however, each service provider must agree to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of the information involved.

  *  **Legal Purposes.** We may share your information when we believe in good faith that such sharing is reasonably necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding possible illegal activities or to comply with legal process.  We may also share your information in situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Service; or to respond to the claims of violation of the rights of third parties and/or to protect the rights, property and safety of Emagine, our employees, users, or the public. This may involve the sharing of your information with law enforcement, government agencies, courts, and/or other organizations.

  *  **Business Transactions.** As we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses, or sell some or all of our assets. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets.  You may have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if, in our discretion, the new entity plans to handle your information in a way that differs materially from this Privacy Policy.

  * We may share your information in any other circumstances where we have your consent.

  4.  **Online Analytics and Tailored Advertising**

 ** _Online Analytics_** **.   **We may use third-party web analytics services on our Services, such as those provide by Google Analytics.  These service providers use the sort of technology described in the Automatically-Collected Information section above to help us analyze how users use the Services, including by noting the third-party website from which you arrive.  The information collected by the technology will be disclosed to or collected directly by these service providers, who use the information to evaluate your use of the Services.  To prevent Google Analytics from using your information for analytics, you may install the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser by [clicking here](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

 ** _Tailored Online Advertising_** **.   **Third parties whose products or services are accessible or marketed via the Services may also place cookies or other tracking technologies on your computer or other device to collect information about your use of the Services, in order to (i) inform, optimize, and serve advertising content based on past visits to our Services and other sites and (ii) report how our advertising content impressions, other uses of advertising services, and interactions with these advertising impressions and services are related to visits to our Services. We also may allow other third parties (e.g., ad networks, servers and platform) to serve tailored advertising to you on the Services or on other websites or in other mobile applications, and to access their own cookies or other tracking technologies on your computer or other device you use to access the Services. We neither have access to, nor does this Privacy Policy govern, the use of cookies or other tracking technologies that may be placed by such third parties. If you are interested in more information about tailored browser advertising and how you can generally control cookies from being put on your computer or mobile browser to deliver tailored advertising (i.e., not just for the Services), you may visit the [Network Advertising Initiative’s Consumer Opt-Out Link ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) and/or the [Digital Advertising Alliance’s Consumer Opt-Out Link](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) to opt-out of receiving tailored advertising from companies that participate in those programs. Please note that to the extent advertising technology is integrated into the Services, you may still receive advertising content even if you opt-out of tailored advertising.  In that case, the advertising content will just not be tailored to your interests.  Also, we do not control any of the above opt-out links and are not responsible for any choices you make using these mechanisms or the continued availability or accuracy of these mechanisms.

  5.  **Information Access.**

Through your account settings, you may access and, in some cases, change information in your profile.  The information you can view and update through your account settings may change as the Services change.

  6.  **How We Protect Information.**

We have implemented appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access to your information and to maintain data security. These safeguards take into account the sensitivity of the information that we collect, process and store and the current state of technology.  Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of or access to your information, the Internet and the Services are not 100% secure so we cannot guarantee that your information we collect or store will be protected from all unauthorized access or disclosure and thereby used in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

  7.  **Communication Choices.**

Information collected on our Services is used for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy, and is subject to the choices discussed throughout this Privacy Policy.  We provide opt-out information in all commercial email messages via an “unsubscribe” link.  Please note that it may take us some time to process your requests consistent with applicable law.  You do not have the ability to opt-out of non-commercial communications that we send if you are enrolled in our rewards or membership programs or if you have engaged in transactions with us (such as service announcements and administrative or informational messages).

  8.  **Linked Sites and Services.**

Our Services may contain links to third-party websites, including social media services. Your use of these features may result in the collection, processing or sharing of information about you, depending on the feature. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites or services which may be linked on our Services. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party websites or services. The information you choose to provide to or that is collected by these third parties is not covered by our Privacy Policy. We strongly encourage you to read such third parties’ privacy policies.

  10.  **Children.**

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly allow such persons to use our Services. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to use the Services or send any us any information.  In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verified parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible.  If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us using the contact information below.

  11.  **How to Contact Us.**

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy or practices, please visit our contact page located here:  [http://www.emagine-entertainment.com/contact/](https://www.emagine-entertainment.com/contact-us/).

  12.  **Changes to this Policy.**

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes in the law, our data collection and use practices, the features of our Services, or advances in technology.  Please check this page periodically for changes.  Use of information we collect is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used.  Your continued use of our services following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will mean you consent to and accept those changes.
